



MAHDI KAANICHE

Wordpress & Js Developer

My name is Mahdi, Originally from Tunisia, Passionate about Web Technologies. For the past 3 years, I have been working as a Full Stack Web Developer. I have a diverse set of skills ranging from Design, Frontend, CMS using a variety of languages such as Javascript and PHP and their modern frameworks. The ability to learn fast and elevate me to new challenges that what makes me stand out

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCER ON FIVERR (2018-2022)

FREELANCER ON UPWORK (2020-2022)

Part time WordPress developer

DIGITAL-PILOT.CA (01/03/2021 - 01/08/-2021)

 Managing multiple WordPress websites including Migration to new servers, Adding design details using multiple themes and building tools and fixing daily bugs

JS & WordPress developer SHOWTAG (01/08/2021 - UNTIL NOW)

- Worked with a team to refine the design and optimize the performance of the website
- Used HTML, CSS, and JavaScript, WordPress ,Elementor to contribute to a full revamp of the showtag website

CONTACT

Email: contact@mahdiwebi.com

Phone: +216 26 194 035

Address: Tunisia

Website: www.mahdiwebi.com

SKILLS

Visual Basic, JavaScript, React, express, HTML, CSS, , WordPress

LANGUAGES

ENGLISH(Fluent)

FRENCH(basic)

EDUCATION

UNIVERSITY OF ART (SFAX) 2017-2018

DÉVELOPPEMENT DE SYSTÈMES 2018-2021 INTELLIGENTS ET DE INFORMATIQUE INDUSTRIELS